cookingforengineers.com 2017-12-11

# Privacy Policy - Privacy Policy - Cooking For Engineers

Last updated October 2015 

**How We Collect and Use Information**

_Analytics information_. Cooking For Engineers uses third-party analytics tools to help measure traffic and usage trends. These tools collect information sent normally by your browser as part of a web page request, including the pages you visit, your browser information, and other information that may help us improve Cooking For Engineers. We use this analytics information in aggregate form such that it cannot reasonably be manipulated to identify any particular individual user. 

_Cookies_. Like nearly all but the simplest websites, Cooking For Engineers uses cookies - a small piece of text data stored on your browser. A cookie is used by Cooking For Engineers to distinguish between different users (for example, cookies are what allows users to log into websites) and occassionally store state information (for example, changing a setting on the website may result in a cookie being saved to your browser to remember the new setting). Advertisers on Cooking For Engineers may also use their own cookies to help them keep track of different users and pages visited on Cooking For Engineers. Cookie settings can be altered in your own browser's settings. 

_Location data_. When you access Cooking For Engineers from a mobile device, we may access and save "location data", which may include GPS coordinates (e.g. latitude and/or longitude) or similar information regarding the location of your mobile device. Location data is important for both advertising and some features of Cooking For Engineers. 

**Sharing Your Information**   
1\. We do not sell or give out your personal information, email address, or any other information to third parties.   
2\. We might provide some personally identifiable information with third-party business partners for the purpose of providing a service to you (for example, if we were to start a mailing list, we may provide emails to a mail service or when we raffle off prizes mailing addresses may be provided to a third party to drop shit the prize). Those business partners will be given limited access to the personally identifiable information that is reasonably necessary to deliver service, and we will require that such third parties comply with this Privacy Policy. 

**Children's Policy**   
Cooking For Engineers does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from persons under thirteen years of age. If you are under 13, please do not attempt to register for this website or send any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, or email address. No one under age 13 may provide any personal information to or on Cooking For Engineers. 

**Other Websites and Services**   
We are not responsible for the practices employed by websites or services linked to or from Cooking For Engineers. Please remember that when you use a link to go from Cooking For Engineers to another website, our Privacy Policy does not apply to third-party websites or services. Those websites and services will have their own policies. This Privacy Policy only applies to information collected through this website. You are responsible for all of your activity in connection with and accessing Cooking For Engineers. Cooking For Engineers is not responsible for the content of linked sites. 

Published on October 15, 2015 at 04:37 AM
